Good evening!
You 're watching South
Africa Why So Serious
News.
I 'm Dan — here 's your
daily dose of drama.
Deputy Police Minister
Castle Matale has
described the police
minister 's decision to
disband the political
killings task team as ``
highly irregular.
'' Only in SA can
operational challenges be
solved by simply
ignoring them!
Meanwhile, at the
Madlanga Commission, forensic
analysts are busy
clarifying discrepancies,
proving once again that
crime scene evidence is
just a suggestion.
Another plot twist!
In other news, the DA
has launched a bold
proposal to scrap the
Black Economic
Empowerment policy,
claiming it benefits only
the elite.
Because who needs
economic growth when you can
just change the rules?
As we gear up for the
G20 summit, Mayor Leagaza
is confident South
Africa will shine.
Let ’ s hope the only
thing that gets lost is
the Wi-Fi signal!
That 's your daily dose
of drama — where the
scandals are serious,
but the anchor is n't.
Goodnight, Mzansi.